<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<versioninfo latestversion="0.8.2.3" latestversionfolder="gamefiles" latestversionfilelist="filelist.xml">
  <patchnotes>
    <patchnote version="0.8.2.3">
- Clients can now join servers that have an IPv6 address.
- Added "unban" and "unbanip" commands.
- Fixed a bunch of bugs that were causing "attempted to apply an invalid force/impulse to a physics body" errors.
- Fixed a bunch of bugs that were causing "attempted to move a pulljoint extremely far" errors.
- Fixed DebugConsole selecting non-command lines if up/down is pressed when there are no commands in the console.
- Fixed inventory syncing not working on the controlled character's inventory if the character is unconscious or wearing handcuffs.
- Verify that the launched exe belongs to the currently selected content package when starting up the game.
- Fixed console messages that have been created before initializing the debug console not being present in crash logs. Made it difficult to diagnose crashes that occur immediately when the game starts.
- Additional error logging to diagnose SharpDX errors on startup.
    </patchnote>
    <patchnote version="0.8.2.2">
- Fixed clients not seeing explosions from items that explode on impact or when their condition reaches zero.
- Fixed conditionals being ignored on delayed status effects.
- Fixed clients staying in an unsynced state if they rejoin while their character is dead or unconscious,causing the camera not to follow the character and preventing the player from giving up.
- Fixed LightComponent sprites and broken device sprites not being mirrored in mirrored subs.
- Fixed a few ragdoll animation bugs that caused "attempted to move pulljoint anchor extremely far" errors.
- Fixed AI characters (most often mantises) being able to attack through walls.
- Fixed alien ruins occasionally overlapping with each other or being above the upper boundary of the level.
- Docking ports automatically stretch the hulls between them to cover the area between the docked subs. Otherwise there may be areas uncovered by hulls if the docking port is positioned slightly outside the extents of the submarine's hulls, causing characters to implode or get thrown back when they try to pass from sub to another.
- Fixed client-side docking ports creating duplicate bodies on doors, causing characters to collide with an invisible door when trying to move between docked subs (until the server forces them through it).
- Fixed characters occasionally getting teleported outside the sub for a few frames when moving between docked subs.
- Fixed status effects that deplete oxygen affecting characters that don't need air to breathe.
- More error logging to diagnose syncing errors.
- Melee weapons can only hit one character per swing (makes stun batons and medical syringes less OP).
- Option to make RegEx component only send a signal when it receives a signal (not continuously according to the last received signal).
- Added FalseOutput property to RegEx components.
    </patchnote>
  </patchnotes>
</versioninfo>